[EP23]
Shoot!
Xiao Wan,
aim at my heart
for the next shot.
Can I
understand that
you love me,
so you didn't kill me,
and just shot me in the leg,
not in the heart?
Chu Nanfeng,
I don't understand why you have to
fight Ling Shenxing for everything,
including me.
Because
power is a good thing.
My parents always taught me to be humble.
Nanfeng,
being humble is not to wrong yourself,
but to care about others.
That's the magnanimity of our family.
[Nanfeng, you'll be a gentleman.]
[A gentleman should be modest.]
[Giving up what you love]
[to others is the most decent thing.]
[Don't be capricious.]
[A good child should know]
[how to behave and give in.]
[But I find only those with power can be themselves.]
Father.
The Southwestern Departments are coveting our land.
If our soldiers have no food,
how can they fight?
That's not your concern.
Father,
one wrong step
leads to another.
Do we want to be condemned by history?
History is written
by those in power.
You've learned nothing
of the gentleman's way I taught you.
The Lings hold military power.
Yet you go against them.
Are you trying to ruin our family?
You've offended them.
What about your brother?
What about the Chus?
Power.
It's a good thing.
Ridiculous.
Chu Nanfeng.
Do you remember the third drink
when we first met?
Horse's Neck,
also known as Jin Ma Jing in Chinese,
signifying honesty
and keeping one's word.
That drink
also has another meaning,
which is to not play tricks.
I've always been
straightforward with you.
Jinrou should have found the plague prescription.
The people of Yang City will be saved.
Kill him!
The plague has spread throughout the city.
You monster!
You deserve it!
Yes, kill him!
Shoot him!
Shoot his whole family!
Kill him!
Yes, kill him!
Kill him! He caused the plague in our city!
Young Marshal,
in the next life,
I'll still be your subordinate.
I don't regret
following you.
Stop!
Move!
Su Muwan?
Why is she here?
Second Auntie,
are you surprised
to see Deputy Zhang?
You thought you poisoned him,
he would lose his memory
and won't tell your secret.
Wipe your sweat.
What's going on?
Deputy Zhang,
you have asthma.
I still remember.
Second Concubine, let me ask you.
Is Ling Shenkang
really the son of you and Commander Ling?
Is he the blood of the Ling family?
Shenkang is the son of me and the commander.
He is the young master of the Ling family.
I'm talking about
you had an affair with Deputy Zhang
and gave birth to Ling Shenkang.
You two worked together
to kill Commander Ling.
and tried to frame the Sus.
You thought poisoning Zhang
would silence him,
but he would've exposed your secrets.
Not only that,
you and Chu Nanfeng
poisoned Yang City's water source,
creating a plague
to weaken the Lings.
Right?
They control all of Yang City's water.
Yang City.
Water source.
No wonder the plague spread so fast.
This is really ridiculous.
Where's the evidence?
Who would believe
your empty words?
Evidence?
Deputy Zhang is the evidence.
And
asthma.
Deputy Zhang has asthma.
So does Ling Shenkang.
And this disease
is highly hereditary.
No one in the Ling family
has ever had
asthma.
Give me the child.
Give me.
You bitch.
You can do such a thing
to tarnish the family's reputation.
I've always been curious
why Old Madam Ling
smells of Ghost Vine.
I thought
it was because you accidentally
got it on her when you poisoned me.
Now I understand.
It's not an accident.
You've been
but
you have been poisoning her.
You poison woman.
How dare you poison me?
Mom.
She's framing me.
She's so good at talking.
You have to believe me.
Second Aunt,
look at this.
I found the letters
I found the love letters
between you and Zhang.
It's full of
your ambition to take over the Ling family
and how to kill the Marshal.
Letters can be forged.
Tell me.
What's the benefit
for me to do this?
Benefit?
You can take over the Ling family's fortune
and make your son
the heir of the Ling family.
Is that the benefit you want?
You've been married into the Ling family for so long,
but you didn't have a son.
You were worried about losing your status.
So,
you had an affair with Deputy Zhang
and gave birth to Ling Shenkang.
As for me,
I accidentally found out about your affair,
Then you killed me
and framed the Sus.
Don't you think
what a good story it is?
Su Muwan,
you always have a good tongue.
It's a pity that
you don't tell stories.
If you can't provide solid evidence,
shut up.